consolecheatcodes.com 2014-02-13

# Cheat Freak - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Quick Look

  1. Anyone may browse our site, but you must provide personal information in order to register with us and take full advantage of all services that our site has to offer. 
    * Learn more
  2. We may contact you by email or SMS text and we may share your profile information publicly with other GameFly members. 
    * Access Settings to manage your e-mail/mobile preferences 
  3. We set cookies on your Web browser so that we can recognize you and personalize our site to your preferences. 
    * Learn more
  4. We allow our third party advertising partner to set cookies on your Web browser in order to serve targeted advertisements to you on our Website. 
    * Learn more
  5. We allow our network of third party advertising partners to set cookies on your Web browser so that they may recognize you on other Websites and serve you GameFly ads. 
    * Learn more
  6. You can control the placement of cookies on your Web browser for advertising purposes by your Web browser settings. 
    * Learn more

GameFly, Inc. and GameFly Digital, Inc. (collectively, “GameFly,” “we” or “us”) respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and mobile application users. The GameFly Online Privacy Policy (this “Privacy Policy”) provides information about how we collect, store, disclose and use information. Please also review our online Terms of Use, which are linked at the bottom of our web pages and which govern the commercial-transaction, user-generated content and social-networking features of our websites ([gamefly.com](http://www.gamefly.com/), [gamefly.co.uk](http://www.gamefly.co.uk/), [shacknews.com](http://www.shacknews.com/), [cheatfreak.com](http://www.cheatfreak.com/) and [mobygames.com](http://www.mobygames.com/)) and services. 

By reading this Privacy Policy, you can expect to be informed about the following: 

  * What does this Privacy Policy apply to?
  * Use of information that you provide to us 
  * Use of information collected through technology 
  * Disclosure and sharing of information 
  * Can I choose how my personal information is used? 
  * What is the GameFly policy regarding children? 
  * How does GameFly protect my personal information? 
  * Contact Us

## What does this Privacy Policy apply to?

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the online and mobile websites and interactive and mobile applications operated by GameFly (unless a different policy is provided on a particular site or application, in which case such different policy shall control) (collectively, the “Services”), including, but not limited to, the gamefly.com, gamefly.co.uk, shacknews.com, mobygames.com, and cheatfreak.com websites, including all subpages and successor pages thereto (each, a “Website” and collectively, the “Websites”) and the GameFly mobile application and associated services (the “GameFly App,” “Application,” or “App”). Unless expressly provided for, this Privacy Policy does not extend to any websites, applications or services of any third party companies or organizations to which we link or which link to us. GameFly does not operate or control those websites, applications or services. 

Review the privacy policy of any third party website, application or service linked to or accessible from our site before you submit any personal information to such parties. 

GameFly has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this Privacy Policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe’s program requirements including transparency, accountability, and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us at [support@gamefly.com](mailto:support@gamefly.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact TRUSTe. 

GameFly complies with the U.S. – E.U. Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. - Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from individuals located in European Union member countries and Switzerland. GameFly has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view GameFly’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>. 

We reserve the right, in our sole and absolute discretion, to make changes from time to time (with or without notice) to this Privacy Policy. As such, you should review this Privacy Policy periodically to check for updates. When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “last updated” date located at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. For changes to this Privacy Policy that we consider to be material, we will place a notice on the website by revising the link to read substantially as “Updated Privacy Policy” for a reasonable amount of time or contact you by email (sent to the email address listed in your account). If you provide information to us or access or use the Website or the Services in any way after this Privacy Policy has been changed, you will be deemed to have unconditionally consented and agreed to such changes. The most current version of this Privacy Policy will be available on the website and will supersede all previous versions of this Privacy Policy. 

By using or accessing the Website and/or the Services, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, delete all cookies from your browser cache after visiting or using the Website and/or Services and do not visit or use the Website or Services thereafter. Your continued use of the Website and/or Services will signify your acceptance of these terms. 

## Use of information that you provide to us

Typically, we ask you to submit personal, financial and/or demographic information if you decide to: 

  * Register for and use a Shacknews and/or GameFly Account (e.g., to rent or buy games, sign-up for newsletters or participate in social activity and sharing) 
  * Register for and use GameFly Applications
  * Use our GameFly Referrals feature
  * Use our GameFly Mobile Alerts feature
  * Use our Buy Alerts feature
  * “Contact Us”

To simply browse our Website or applications, you are not required to provide any personal information. However, if you choose not to submit personal information when requested to do so, you may not be able to access some or all of the services that we provide. 

###  Shacknews and GameFly Account Registration 

To create a Shacknews and/or GameFly account, we ask you for certain personally identifiable information, which may include your full name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, and billing information (such as a credit card number). We may also ask you to create a password and to provide other information such as your gender, game and platform preferences (e.g., about the games and hardware you own), hobbies and interests, and other information (including “demographic information”) as part of your user profile - we may link this demographic information to your personal information. 

When you download and use our Services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and device identifier (or “UDID”). 

Once collected, we use the information above to:

  1. create, confirm and give you access to your Shacknews and/or GameFly account
  2. process and ship your GameFly orders
  3. communicate with you (via e-mail, SMS, MMS, or voice) about the status of your orders or to provide Buy Alerts and SMS/MMS messages you request
  4. answer any requests that you may have
  5. send you Shacknews and/or GameFly newsletters that you have chosen to receive
  6. serve advertisements to your Web browser that we believe may be of interest to you ( _see“Online Advertising Practices” below for more information_)

We may also use your Shacknews and/or GameFly account e-mail address to send you service-related announcements that tell you about updates to our Privacy Policy or Terms of Use, new areas or features on the Services, changes to our online service or technical support policies, and other related changes. We may also use your personal and demographic information aggregated with other members’ information for our internal marketing and demographic studies, so we can improve the online products and services we provide you and to better meet your needs. 

If you want to be excluded from receiving promotional email communications, you may unsubscribe via the opt-out link embedded in the communication or by logging in to Settings and updating your E-mail Subscription preferences. 

### GameFly App Usage

When using GameFly social features (including user reviews, following users, and status updates), we may ask for certain personally identifiable information, including your full name, email address, user name, password and birthday. We ask you to provide other information as part of your “bio” or “profile,” such as your gender, location (city and state only), and social network URLs and to create a user picture/avatar to display to others on the App. We may also collect your unique device identifier and your telephone number and location if you have activated the GPS function on your mobile device. We use this for display purposes. You may opt-out of having your location information used by us at any time by turning it off at the device level. The foregoing information is used to identify you to us and other users as a GameFly App user and to allow you to access the functionality provided on the App, such as posting messages and receiving App updates (e.g., when another App user responds to one of your posts, etc.). Note that you can link the information contained in your GameFly and App accounts. 

You can use the GameFly App without providing all of the requested information above. The information you do provide may be visible by other App users as part of your profile, but you have the ability to control whether your full name, age and/or gender are displayed - the default settings for these are all set to “Off.” 

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

When your computer or mobile device contacts our web servers (for example, when you visit or use the Services, scan a Microsoft Tag or QR code, or view an HTML e-mail), our web servers automatically collect usage information. Such usage information includes information about how our visitors use and navigate the Services. It can include the number and frequency of visitors to the Services and the length of their stays, browser type, referrer data that identifies the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting our website or using the Services, and IP addresses (see below for more information on IP addresses). We also may determine the applicable technology available in order to serve you the most appropriate version of a web page, e-mail, advertising or promotional announcement or similar service. This information is used to analyze and improve the Services, and to provide you with a more fulfilling and relevant experience. 

### GameFly Referrals

When you use the GameFly Referrals Program (or the “Referral Program”), we may ask you to provide your and your friends’ first names and e-mail addresses. This information is used to email them a one-time promotional communication offering a free GameFly trial membership or discount pre-paid membership, and the opportunity to make further referrals to their friends. If opted in, you and/or your friends may receive additional communications from us or our vendors in relation to the Referral Program and your and/or your friends’ participation in it. The data collected through the Referral Program is used only for the operation and ongoing maintenance of the Referral Program and will not be used for any other purpose or distributed to any third parties other than those GameFly vendors retained to operate and maintain the Referral Program. 

You and your friends may opt-out of participation in the Referral Program at any time via the opt-out links in the communications sent to you and your friends, or by sending an e-mail to us at [friends_optout@gamefly.com](mailto:friends_optout@gamefly.com). 

### GameFly Mobile Alerts

You may sign up to receive GameFly Mobile Alerts on your mobile device that inform you when GameFly has shipped and received your game rentals. When you sign up to receive GameFly Mobile Alerts, we ask you to submit the mobile phone number to which you would like the alerts to be sent. Mobile phone numbers collected on the GameFly Mobile Alerts Preferences page will be used only for delivery of requested mobile alerts, and for no other purpose, and will otherwise be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. When we send Mobile Alerts to you, our service provider may obtain and store information about your carrier and phone make and model, so that they can optimize and deliver our messages to you. That data is only used for message delivery operations and is only shared with other service providers in the message delivery chain. 

By signing up for Mobile Alerts, you agree to pay any fees or costs required by your mobile device provider. You may choose to stop receiving Mobile Alerts via the unsubscribe option in each Mobile Alert sent to you or by logging in to Settings and updating your Mobile Alerts preferences. 

### “Contact Us” Form

If you choose to contact us via our online form, we ask you to provide your first name, e-mail address, and a description of your question or comment. This form is intended for questions and comments only. We use the information you provide solely to respond to your inquiry and for no other purpose. We may retain and aggregate your comments for demographic purposes and to improve our services. 

### Sharing Pages With Friends

The Services may offer you the possibility to connect your accounts from third party social media sites, such as Facebook and Twitter, through an application programming interface (API) or other software. By allowing the Services to connect with your accounts on such third party sites, you may opt to consent to our accessing the information in those accounts, which information may include personally identifiable information. You may likewise consent to our publishing on the Services any such information or actions you take on such third party sites. Additionally, you understand that by accessing the Services via your social media account, activity you engage in through the Services may be published on the third party site. It is your choice whether to use any such third party sites, and you understand that in some instances such third party sites may request to access and publish information about you or your friends that is included in your GameFly account. Third party sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. We recommend you review the privacy policies of each third party site before you share pages or information with your friends through those sites. 

##  Use of information collected through technology 

### Browser Cookies

The Services set browser “cookies” on your computer or other device. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s or mobile device’s hard drive or storage through your Web browser when you visit or use the Services. If cookies are disabled on your Web browser, you will not be able to use many of the functions of the Services. The “Help” menu on most Web browsers will tell you how to enable or disable cookies. 

Please note that information contained in a cookie may be linked to your personally identifiable information via an account ID. Cookies allow us to provide enhanced functionality on the Services, such as: 

  * automatically identifying you when you return to the Services
  * matching the games you’ve chosen to rent or buy with your individual account
  * personalizing our Services for you - e.g., cookies allow us to track your order and billing history automatically from the beginning of your GameFly membership, which allows you to log in to Settings and see a complete list of games you’ve rented or bought from us

In addition, our third party advertising partners will place a unique cookie on your browser via the Services for purposes of serving advertisements when you visit or use the Services or when you visit other non-GameFly websites on the Internet. Please see below for more information about our “Online Advertising Practices.” Our Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by third parties. We do not have access or control over these cookies. 

### Flash Cookies & HTML5

Some of the Services may require the use of the Adobe Flash Player. Adobe’s Flash Player is used by many websites that offer video and other interactive content. By default, your use of the Adobe Flash Player generates “flash cookies” (also known as “persistent identification elements” or “local shared objects”). Adobe provides a short disclosure about Flash Cookies in its End User License Agreement, stating “Use of the web players, specifically the Flash Player, will enable the Software to store certain user settings as a local shared object on our computer. These settings are not associated with you, but allow you to configure certain settings within the Flash Player.” The Adobe Flash Player (and similar applications) use flash cookies to remember user settings, preferences and usage similar to the browser cookies referenced above, but flash cookies can store more information than browser cookies and are managed through a different interface than the one provided by your Web browser. You can control the degree to which you accept flash cookies by accessing your Adobe Flash Player management tools directly through the settings manager for Adobe Flash, located at <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html>. If you do not allow flash cookies to take any space on your computer or device, you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in certain features of the Services. Users with a computer running the Windows operating system can view flash cookie files in this folder: \Documents and Settings\\[username]\Application Data\Macromedia\Flash Player. Users with a computer running the Apple operating system can view flash cookie files in this folder: /users/[username]/Library/Preferences/macromedia/Flash Player. Flash cookies, or LSO files, are stored typically with an “.SOL” extension. 

### IP Addresses

An IP address is a number that is assigned to your device or network when you are linked to the Internet. When you request pages from the Services, our servers log your IP address. We may use IP addresses for a number of purposes, such as system administration, to report aggregate information to our business partners or to audit the use of the Services. We may associate your IP address with the personally identifiable information you provide. 

We also may collect and store information about you that we receive from other sources to enable us to update and correct the information contained in our database and to provide product recommendations and special offers that we think will interest you. 

### Clear GIFs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

Our third party advertising partner employs a software technology called clear GIFs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content in our Services by informing us what content is effective. Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear GIFs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

### Mobile Analytics

We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our mobile software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We may collect age, gender, geolocation, user ID, user profile photo, UDID, username, and IMEI to optimize content and advertising and to measure usage and engagement. 

## Disclosure and sharing of information

We will not sell your information to third parties. We may share your information with third parties as outlined below. 

### Third Party Service Providers

We work with third party companies, agents, and contractors (“Vendors”) to perform some important tasks, such as processing credit card transactions, fulfilling and delivering your orders, operating and maintaining our Referral Program, delivering Mobile Alerts, and marketing/advertising programs. We require that our Vendors maintain the confidentiality of any information about our members that may be disclosed to them and to use such information solely for the purpose of providing the contracted-for services on GameFly’s behalf. 

### External Links

The Services may contain links to, or advertisements about, non-GameFly websites. Other sites may also reference, advertise, or link to the Services. GameFly does not endorse or sponsor other websites, is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of non-GameFly sites, expressly disclaims any statements or assertions made on such websites, and denies all liability associated with your use of, and the content on, such other websites and advertisements. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to information gathered through other websites. We encourage you to be aware of this when you leave the Services and to read the privacy policy of each and every website that you visit. 

Ad Serving Technology: The Services may employ proprietary or third party ad serving technologies that use cookies, clear GIFs, web beacons, tracking pixels or other technologies to collect information as a result of ad serving through the Services. We or third parties operating the ad serving technology may use demographic and location information, as well as information logged from your hardware or device to ensure that appropriate advertising is presented within the Service and to calculate or control the number of unique and repeat views of a given ad, and/or deliver ads that relate to your interests and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns. We or third parties may collect data for this purpose, including your IP address (including for purposes of determining your approximate geographic location), device ID, information about your software, applications and hardware, machine or device make and model, advertisement(s) served, in game location, length of time an advertisement was visible, other Internet and website usage information, web pages and mobile Internet sites which have been viewed by you (as well as date and time), domain type, size of the advertisement, advertisement response (if any), and angle of view. Note that if you click on an ad that appears on the Services, you acknowledge and agree that your name or other identifying characteristics may be revealed to the advertiser (or its ad server) through referrer headers (the URL transmitted by publishers when users click on ads). 

You recognize and agree that the advertising companies who deliver ads for GameFly may combine the information collected with other information they have independently collected from other services or products. These companies collect and use information under their own privacy policies. These ad serving technologies may be integrated into the Services. 

Advertising Third Party Products & Services: The third party ads appearing on the Website are delivered to your browser by DoubleClick via Future US, our Web advertising partner. DoubleClick (or a similar third party vendor) may set and access its own cookies on your Web browser in order to serve ads it believes may be of interest to you based on the profile information you provided to us at registration (e.g., demographic information) as well as information collected about you by DoubleClick elsewhere on the Web. DoubleClick (or a similar third party vendor) may use information about you gathered from the Services (including your demographic information provided to us upon registration as well as your browsing behavior on the Website) to serve third party ads to you elsewhere on the Internet. DoubleClick’s (or a similar third party vendor’s) use of cookies on our Website is subject to DoubleClick’s (or a similar third party vendor’s) privacy policies. For more information about DoubleClick and how cookies work, please visit [DoubleClick’s website](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) and the [Network Advertising Initiative’s homepage](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), or [TRUSTe’s preference manager](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please see “Can I choose how my personal information is used?” below to learn more about setting your Web browser to block cookies. 

The third party ads appearing on the App are delivered to you by AdMarvel (or a similar third party vendor). AdMarvel serves ads it believes may be of interest to you. For more information about Ad Marvel and the privacy policies that govern its advertising practices please visit [Ad Marvel’s website](http://www.admarvel.com/). 

Advertising GameFly Products & Services: After you visit or use the Services, our advertising partners may deliver GameFly ads to your Web browser when you are visiting other sites on the Internet. These ads are delivered based on cookies that are set by our third party advertising network partners when you visit or use the Services, and that are recognized by these companies when you visit other sites. Please see “Can I choose how my personal information is used?” below to learn more about setting your Web browser to block cookies. 

The Services may contain links to other sites where third parties may collect, store or share information about you. We clearly mark those links on the Services so you will know if you are submitting your information to a third party (e.g., to a social network such as Facebook or Twitter). In addition, you may have the option to enable sharing specific actions automatically to a social network. If you have opted in to automatic sharing, you will not be notified by GameFly each time a sharing action occurs. As noted above, GameFly does not operate or control those third party sites, so please review the privacy policy of any linked site before providing any personal information or using any feature of a social networking site that is linked to the Services. 

Through the Services, you can connect with friends, display your game rentals and purchases; discuss games with the community of users, follow or be-followed-by other gamers; and engage in other aspects of social networking. As noted above, some of your personal information, such as your name, and other profile information, may be displayed publicly to other members of the Services. You can control the information that is publicly displayed to the Services community by managing your Privacy Settings in the Services; and you can control whether to publicly post a message or whether you have added/bought/kept a game. 

The Services include social media features (“Features”), such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address and information about which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

You can log in to our site using third party services like Facebook or Twitter. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. These services also give you the option to post information about your activities on this Website and to your social network in order to share with others within your network. 

### Public Forums

Our Website offers publicly accessible user-generated content. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [support@gamefly.com](mailto:support@gamefly.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know that we are unable to do so and why. 

### Co-Sponsors and Promotional Partners

We may run or co-sponsor contests, special offers, or other events or activities (“Events”) on the Services. Information collected for these Events may include personally identifiable information (e.g., name, mailing address, etc.) and may be collected by or shared with a third party sponsor, co-sponsor, or other third party (e.g., promotional partner, retailer, or game or magazine publisher). If you provide information to participate in such Events, we cannot control the third parties’ use of your information. If you do not want your information to be collected by or shared with a third party, do not participate in these optional Events. 

From time to time, we are approached by third party companies and organizations that provide game-related special offers or other offers that we believe may be of interest to you. To extend these offers to you, we may use your Shacknews and/or GameFly account information to send out promotional mailings to you on their behalf. If you select to sign up for the third party offer, we will share your Shacknews and/or GameFly account information with the third party offer provider. We see this as a value-added service helping you find useful products or services. We will not share your information with the third party offer provider unless you chose to take advantage of the third party offer. If you wish to opt-out from third party sharing you may do so by contacting us at [support@gamefly.com](mailto:support@gamefly.com). 

In some instances, we may have an arrangement with a promotional partner or retailer, whereby they share with us customer information collected on their website. In the event that we receive such data and combine it with our customer records, the combined information will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Otherwise, all such information is subject to the privacy policy under which it was collected. 

###  Disclosure and/or Transfer of Personal Information 

We may disclose any or all personal or non-personal information related to you to support an investigation or if we have a good faith belief that it is required by law, including but not limited to requests pursuant to subpoena or court order or similar legal process, and/or disclosure to local, state, or federal law enforcement, or other government officials pursuant to investigations they are conducting, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. In addition, in the event of a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, or other similar event, any customer information in our possession may be transferred to our successor or assignee. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information in connection with such transfer, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 

##  Can I choose how my personal information is used? 

If you wish to view or update the personal information set forth in your account, such as your name, e-mail address, password, billing address, credit card number, e-mail subscription preferences, or other account information, log in to Settings. There is a link to Settings on most pages of the Shacknews Website. Please note that you must log in with your username/e-mail address and password before you can update any account information. If you believe that your account information contains errors, and you cannot correct those errors from the Settings page, please contact Customer Service. Our normal response time to your account questions is within 4 business days. Please be sure to include an email or phone number where you can be reached so we can promptly assist you. 

We will retain your information (including geo-location data) for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [support@gamefly.com](mailto:support@gamefly.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

If you wish to opt out of receiving the Shacknews newsletter, special offers, and/or promotional information, log in to Settings and change your E-mail Subscriptions; or, contact [support@gamefly.com](mailto:support@gamefly.com). In addition, at the bottom of every Shacknews communication sent to you, we provide you an unsubscribe or opt-out link to discontinue receiving future communications (i.e., unsubscribe). 

If you wish to not disclose information to other Services users, log in to the Services to manage your Privacy settings and turn displays to “Off.” 

If you wish to opt out of having cookies set on your Web browser for purposes of online advertising, the only way to ensure that this happens is to manage the settings on your Web browser to delete all cookies and then disallow the further acceptance of cookies. Preventing your browser from accepting cookies prevents GameFly and our advertising partners from tracking you or your browsing behavior. However, it may also disable or interfere with features on the Services. We recommend that you leave cookies “turned on” so we can offer you a better experience using the Services. However, if you wish to prevent cookies from being accepted, most internet browsers allow you to do so. Your Web browser may also be able to alert you when a website or company is about to set a cookie on your browser for tracking and/or advertising purposes. For more information, please refer to your browser’s technical information and visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/), which is a helpful informational site on cookies. 

## What is the GameFly policy regarding children?

You must be 18 years or older to create a GameFly account and become a member. While children under the age of 18 may utilize the GameFly video game rental/purchase service, they may do so only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian and subject to our Terms of Use. We encourage parents to use our Parental Controls feature, which will allow you to control which games your child can rent or purchase under your account. Therefore, if a parent or guardian is the account holder and manages Parental Controls, the account password should not be disclosed to the child. Note that the Services are not directed at collecting information from children under the age of 13, nor are they intended to be used by children under the age of 13. If we receive notice that we have inadvertently collected information from a child under 13, we will take all reasonable steps to delete the information collected from that child. 

##  How does GameFly protect my personal information? 

GameFly employs security technologies and procedures to protect the confidentiality, security, and integrity of the personal information collected from visitors and users of the Services. GameFly uses a secure server to encrypt all of your personal information. The secure server employs Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption, which is an industry standard method of encryption. We have also implemented reasonable security guidelines for our employees, partners, and vendors. We will continue to update and enhance our security practices as new technology becomes available. 

While we take steps to ensure the security of your personal information, no data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, please be aware that when you submit information to us, you do so at your own risk. To further protect your personal information, we ask that you play an important role as well. Take care to prevent unauthorized persons from learning any of your GameFly account information. 

You are solely responsible for safeguarding your GameFly and GameFly App e-mail logins and passwords. To prevent unauthorized use of your accounts, be sure to change your password often, and keep it in a safe place. 

##  Notice to California Residents/Your California Privacy Rights 

California residents are entitled once a year to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year (e.g., responses to requests made in 2012 will contain information about 2011 sharing activities). California residents may request further information about our compliance with this law by sending a request to the address set forth in the Contact Us section below. You must include “California Privacy Rights” in the subject line, and your full name, e-mail address, and postal address in your request. Please note that under California law, businesses are only required to respond to a customer request once during any calendar year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this physical mailing address. 

If you have any questions, complaints, or comments regarding this Privacy Policy or our information collection, storage, disclosure and use practices, please e-mail or contact us at: 

Attn: Vice President, Customer Service  
GameFly, Inc.  
P.O. Box 200533  
Austin, Texas 78720  
1-888-986-6400 - M - F, 12 p.m. - 4 p.m. CST  
[support@gamefly.com](mailto:support@gamefly.com) \- 7 days a week  

Any personal information you provide to the above e-mail or postal mail addresses will not be used to send you promotional materials, unless you request it. 

If you have any questions, complaints or comments regarding our GameFly Referrals Program, please contact [friends_cs@gamefly.com](mailto:friends_cs@gamefly.com). 

Last Updated: June 25, 2013.
